vrzone.com 2017-05-23

# VR-Zone.com Privacy Policy

vr-zone.com, and its advertisers and affiliates are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by vr-zone.com and how it is used. Below is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of consumer information.

All graphics, articles, reviews, etc. on this website is the sole property of vr-zone.com, unless otherwise stated. Any logos, names, slogans, or product pictures are owned by their respective companies, and may be copyrighted. Any sort of use of anything on this webpage may not be used without the permission of vr-zone.com, or else legal action may be taken. Any articles or logos used on the website will be linked to the original website. vr-zone.com will not be held responsible for any misinformation, damage to readers computer systems, or anything damaged as a result of anything published on this webpage. Any hardware or software reviewed is published with the opinion of the author. 

vr-zone.com does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address, unless otherwise stated (A Contest, for example). However, vr-zone.com does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected by vr-zone.com is used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of our advertisers.

Third Party Advertising  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at cs@vrmedia.com.sg. 

Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, vr-zone.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

Cookies and Web Beacons   
vr-zone.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

DoubleClick DART Cookie   
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on vr-zone.com.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to vr-zone.com and other sites on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, IDG TechNetwork, TribalFusion, Burst Media, Admax, Innity.  

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.vr-zone.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

vr-zone.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. vr-zone.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
